ias3.com 2015-03-14

# Privacy Policy : Web Hosting Help Desk

We view your privacy as a very important issue and we do not share your personal information with anyone except to facilitate an order you have made, or as required by law, or to provide you with a product or service at your request or in those limited situations set forth below.

We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website and via the transactions we engage in with you.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our site and services. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. Further information about this is contained in the “Cookies” section below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to our site choose to interact with our site in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with us are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, we collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with our site or services. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our site. However, we do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Third Party Services**

Certain services offered through the Websites are subject to third party privacy policies.  Facebook’s “Like” button is an example of this happens on the Internet.  (and is subject to Facebook’s privacy policies). As a reseller, we may have to disclose information as a condition of being legally able to resell our products and services.

**Content Uploaded to Site.**

Any personal information or picture content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available and you acknowledge that third parties may access, collect and use such content.

**Cookies**

Please note that we may employ the use of cookies.  Such usage of cookies could be when users create user accounts but we may further employ cookies to assist the functionality of other tools, services and functions in the future.

 Cookies are small programs that enhance your use of the Internet, in general, and specifically we use cookies to enhance your usage of our functions.

We use cookies, web beacons, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit our site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests should we offer any.

The information gathered is not shared with third parties. You may turn off your cookies by adjusting the appropriate setting on your browser.

Please consult the HELP menu of your browser to learn how to turn your cookies off. Cookies do not reveal personal information and if you turn off your cookies you may find your enjoyment of the Internet, and our site, to be reduced or impaired. Turning off your cookies may interfere with some of our site’s functions and the site may not appear to be properly working if you turn off your cookies.

In order to seek out and repair functionality issues with our servers and related programming, we may use your email and IP addresses for evaluation and diagnostic purposes.

We will gather site visitors and members IP (Internet Protocol) addresses and aggregate the same so that we can provide demographic information for potential partners, investors or advertisers or for other purposes designed to promote or benefit our web site or business in general. Such information is not personally identifiable in nature.

When you visit this website, we can record certain information in relation to your visit such as:

  * Your IP or proxy server IP;
  * Basic domain information;
  * Your Internet service provider is sometimes captured depending on the configuration of your ISP connection;
  * The date and time of your visit to the website;
  * The length of your session;
  * The pages which you have accessed;
  * The number of times you access our site within any month;
  * The size of file you look at;
  * The website which referred you to our website; and
  * The operating system which your computer uses.

Cookies may provide Recording Session information, show us visitor preferences regarding return visits to our website, help us to mange subscription or private areas on our website, record user specific tracking or aggregate tracking information of visitors and deliver user customized content based on user specific information, such as browser type, screen type and resolution and so forth. None of the information gathered is shared with third parties. These activities are done for the benefit of the site’s user so that we can provide a better, more effective and enjoyable user experience to all users.

Other possible uses for the information that we collect include internal tracking, review, or is used for contacting purposes and then is archived by us for future usage. We also use the information we collect to provide custom content for our user base.

**Compliance with Law Enforcement**

We will cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to legal claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of our company or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of the company and/or its assets, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company.

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred to the purchaser. We may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on our web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets rather than engage in a full acquisition. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred to the purchaser. We may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on our web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at our site, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our site; you consent to the transfer of such information to them.  We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above,  we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our property or legal rights, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of our website and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with our business and our services. We respect your trust in providing us with your email address, so we expect to keep this type of email to a reasonable level. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. We take all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our own company and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Embed Code**

We may install embed code such as but not restricted to google analytics on your website for purposes of monitoring performance and bandwidth usage through your website. Except as expressly specified in these Terms of Service, you may not: (a) copy (except in the course of loading or installing) or modify the Embed Code, including but not limited to adding new features or otherwise making adaptations that alter the functioning of the Embed Code; (b) transfer, sublicense, lease, lend, rent or otherwise distribute the Embed Code to any third party; or (c) disassemble, decompile or reverse engineer the Embed Code, in whole or in part, or permit or authorize a third party to do so, except to the extent such activities are expressly permitted by law notwithstanding this prohibition.

**Further Information on Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on via our business.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

**Google Adsense and Further Cookie Information**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our websites send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.  Our Privacy Policy matches the legal requirements of the United States of America. If you are using our site, tools, or services from outside the United States of America, discontinue from doing so if our privacy policy does not match the requirements of the law in your own jurisdiction.
